{
    "subject": "resource/Murray_S._Blum",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Blum, Murray S.",
    "human_readable": "Murray S. Blum's full name is Blum, Murray S.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9874889254570007,
            "question": "What is Murray S. Blum's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9815048575401306,
            "question": "What is the surname of Murray S. Blum?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9795318841934204,
            "question": "Is 'Murray S. Blum' a common way to abbreviate someone's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9586101770401001,
            "question": "If you were to refer to Murray S. Blum in a formal document, what would his full name be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9538610577583313,
            "question": "Is there a specific order to use when writing Murray S. Blum's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9257521629333496,
            "question": "What is the first name of Murray S. Blum?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8115999102592468,
            "question": "What is the middle initial of Murray S. Blum?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6713327765464783,
            "question": "How should you address Murray S. Blum formally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5750954747200012,
            "question": "If you met Murray S. Blum, how would you introduce yourself?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15894466638565063,
            "question": "Which part of his name comes first?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Murray S. Blum's full name is Blum, Murray S.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1177_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you met Murray S. Blum, how would you introduce yourself?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1177_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How should you address Murray S. Blum formally?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1177_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the middle initial of Murray S. Blum?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1177_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1177_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1177_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1177_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1177_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1177_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1177_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1177_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1177_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1177_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1177_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nExplanation: The documents do not mention that Murray S. Blum's full name is indeed \"Blum, Murray S.\". In fact, the documents suggest that he has multiple names and aliases, including \"Murray L Blum\", \"Murphy Blum\", \"Holly L Nelson\", etc., but they do not confirm his full name as \"Blum, Murray S.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that Murray S. Blum can also be referred to as Blum, Murray S., which aligns with the query \"Murray S. Blum's full name is Blum, Murray S.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There are multiple individuals with the name \"Murray Blum\" mentioned throughout the context information, suggesting that there may be more than one person with this name.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}